(Leonard:)- I can't drive you for the next few weeks.
- No.
(Sheldon:)You said you couldn't drive me to work.
This is from work.
(Leonard:)Howard, help me out here.
(Howard:)No, just for the fun of it,
I'm gonna take his side.
(Sheldon:)Now, how do you propose I get home?
- How did you get here in the first place?
- Penny.
(Sheldon:)But I sense that's no longer an option.
(Leonard:)Look, I need to get to the laser lab.
You're just gonna have to find
someone else to take you home.
(Howard:)Oh, damn. I picked the wrong side.
[SCREAMING]
(Sheldon:)Oh, God, not Euclid Avenue.
(Raj:)Why did Howard leave you
in the middle of the road, anyway?
(Sheldon:)We had a difference of opinion.
(Raj:)Over what?